#### Contact

5166058895 (Home) cmccreig@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/cynthiamccreight-7b2a122b (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Nursing Hospitals BLS

Certifications CCRN

# Cynthia McCreight

Nurse, CCRN | Pilates Trainer New York

# Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing Education, Strategic Planning, Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation (CPR), Intensive Care, and Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS). Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science (B.S.) focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Stony Brook University.

# Experience

Lenox Hill Hospital
CCRN
June 2009 - Present (11 years 3 months)
Cath Lab/MICU

Flex Studio
Pilates trainer
October 2015 - April 2017 (1 year 7 months)
Greater New York City Area

FlexPilates Instructor. Musically driven, pilates based reformer class catered to the client seeking a more challenging workout.

Crunch Fitness Pilates Instructor January 2013 - 2015 (2 years)

SIXTH STREET PILATES, INC.

Pilates Instructor July 2013 - September 2014 (1 year 3 months) new york

Private Pilates Trainer

Mat Pilates Instructor

Northwell Health

#### RN

September 2008 - June 2012 (3 years 10 months)

MICU

# Education

### Maharishi International University

Integrative Ayurvedic Medicine, Ayurvedic Medicine/Ayurveda · (2019 - 2022)

## Exhale Spa

Barre Certified (2017 - 2017)

#### Stony Brook University

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2008 - 2009)

# University of Vermont

Bachelor of Science (BS), Environmental Studies · (2000 - 2005)

## School for International Training

Public Health · (2003 - 2004)